Hyoungjoo Chae

mapoout@yonsei.ac.kr

https://hyungjoo-homepage.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hyungjoo-chae-21236a204

Summary

I am a linked B.S. and M.S. student in Yonsei University. My research insterests include Dialogue Systems, Task-Oriented Dialogues, and Commnsense Reasoning. I love solving real life problems and I am very open-minded to collaborating with others.

Employment History

July 2022 – present

Tutoring, Market Designers Inc. Supervisor: Prof. Jinyoung Yeo

Jul 2020 – Aug 2020

Dino Plus Inc. Engaged in a project, constructed dementia dataset for AI diagnosis

Feb 2021 - Sep 2021

Apgujeong Dr.Choi's clinic Developed company's homepage as a Project Owner. using React.js and Firebase framework.

Education

Feb 2019 – present

Linked B.S. and M.S. Program, Computer Science, Yonsei University

Publications

TUTORING: Instruction-grounded Conversational Agent for Language Learners

Hyungjoo Chae, Minjin Kim, Chaehyeong Kim, Won Seok Jeong, Hye Soong Kim, June Myung Lee, Jinyoung Yeo

In Proceedings of AAAI 2023.

Mind the Gap! Injecting Commonsense Knowledge for Abstractive Dialogue Summarization Seungone Kim*, Se June Joo*, Hyungjoo Chae*, Chae Hyeong Kim*, Seung-won Hwang, Jinyoung Yeo In Proceedings of COLING 2022.

Projects

• Building a Conversational Agent for Language Learners

Built an AI English tutor as a leader of a team in Tutoring. And publish it as a conference paper at AAAI-23 demonstrations.

• Generating English Exam Questions using GPT-3 and SBERT

Proposed a framework which generates English exam questions. https://github.com/kyle8581/QERT

• BiDAF implementation

Implemented BiDAF from scratch. https://github.com/kyle8581/BiDAF

MPAA rating with BERT and LongFormer

Predicted movie rating with BERT and LongFormer. https://github.com/kyle8581/MPAA_rating_with_BERT

• SG-MLP: Switch Gated Multi-Layer Perceptron Model for Natural Language Understanding Implemented SG-MLP and finetuned it on GLEU benchmark. https://github.com/kyle8581/sgMLP_Implementation

Competition Experience

reached the finals, MAIC: Voice AI Challenge 2021.

Jooyeong Jung Startup Competition (team name: Eng-PT).

2019 Crypto Analysis Contest 2019.

Skills

Programming Languages

Deep Learning

Web Dev

Others

Python, Java, C/C++, JavaScript.

PyTorch, Tensorflow, CUDA.

React.js, Firebase, Node.js, Django, Socket Programming, HTML, CSS.

OpenGL, Unity, Figma, AdobeXD, BeutifulSoup, OpenMP